"Bruno Mars - Leave the Door Open [Official Video]"
♪ ♪ ♪ ♪
♪ What you doin (what you doin) ♪
♪ Where you at (where you at) ♪
♪ Oh you got plans (you got plans) ♪
♪ Don't say that (shut yo trap) ♪
♪ I'm sippin wine (sip sip) ♪
♪ In a robe (drip rip) ♪
♪ I look too good (look too good) ♪
♪ To be alone (wooohooo) ♪
♪ My house clean (house clean) ♪
♪ My pool warm (pool warm) ♪
♪ Just shaved (smooth like a new born) ♪
♪ We should be dancing,romancing ♪
♪ In the east wing and the west wing ♪
♪ Of this mansion, wus happenin ♪
♪ I aint playin no games, Every word that I say ♪
♪ Is coming straight from the heart ♪
♪ (so if you tryna lay in these arms) ♪
♪ Imma leave the door open (imma leave the door open) ♪
♪ Imma leave the door open girl ♪
♪ (Imma leave the door open, open) ♪
♪ That you feel the way I feel ♪
♪ And you want me like I want you tonight baby ♪
♪ (tell me that you're coming through) ♪
♪ You're so sweet(so sweet) ♪
♪ So tight(so tight) ♪
♪ I won't bite(ahh ahh) ♪
♪ Unless you like(unless you like) ♪
♪ If you smoke(what you smoke) ♪
♪ I got that haze(purple haze) ♪
♪ And if you're hungrygirl I got filets (woohooo) ♪
♪ Ooh baby don't keep me waiting ♪
♪ There's so much love we could be making ♪
♪ I'm talking kissing, Cuddling ♪
♪ Rose pedals in the bathtub ♪
♪ Lets jump in, Its bubblin ♪
♪ I aint playin no games ♪
♪ Every word that I say  ♪
♪ Is coming straight from the heart ♪
♪ (so if you tryna lay in these arms) ♪
♪ Imma leave the door open (imma leave the door open) ♪
♪ Imma leave the door open girl ♪
♪ (Imma leave the door open, open) ♪
♪ That you feel the way I feel ♪
♪ And you want me like I want you tonight baby ♪
♪ (tell me that you're coming through) ♪
♪ La la laaa la la la la la (I need you baby) ♪
♪ La la laaa la la la la (I gotta see you baby) ♪
♪ La la laaa la la la la ♪
♪ (Girl I'm tryna give you this) ♪
♪ (aaaaahhhhhhhhhh) ♪
♪ Imma leave my door open (imma leave the door open) ♪
♪ Imma leave my door open girl ♪
♪ (Imma leave the door open, open) ♪
♪ And I'm hopin', hopin' ♪
♪ That you feel the way I feel ♪
♪ And you want me like I want you tonight baby ♪
♪ (tell me that you're coming through) ♪
♪ La la laaa la la la la la (tell me somethin') ♪
♪ (wooohooo) ♪
♪ La la laaa la la la la la ♪
♪ (tell me that you're coming through) ♪
♪ Girl I'm here just waiting for you ♪
♪ Come on over I'll adore you ♪
♪ La la laaa la la la la la I'm waiting for you ♪
♪ Girl I'm here just waiting for you ♪
♪ Come on over I'll adore you ♪
♪ La la laaa la la la la la ♪
♪ (Music fades) ♪
Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com